(Raj:)I think you'd be pleased to hear that
this morning in the parking garage,
(Raj:)I saw this oil stain on the ground
that was shaped just like
(Raj:)my ex-girlfriend, Lucy,
and I didn't get upset at all.
(Howard:)I'm proud of you.
(Raj:)Well, you should be,
'cause she was looking good.
Dear Lord!
You're an astronomer.
(Sheldon:)Although you may have earthly woes,
get your mind back on the stars.
(Sheldon:)Gee, even the lowly dung beetle
chooses to plot its course
(Sheldon:)-by using the Milky Way.
-Is that true?
(Sheldon:)Everything I say is true.
(Sheldon:)Now, of course,
the dung beetle also enjoys
eating feces, living in feces
and making little balls out of feces.
(Sheldon:)So, you know, pick and choose
which aspects of its lifestyle
(Sheldon:)you want to embrace.
(Howard:)Come on, you can talk to girls now.
(Howard:)It shouldn't be hard for you
to meet someone new.
(Raj:)How can I meet someone new when
everywhere I look, I see Lucy's face?
(Raj:)Tell me you don't see her smile
in the crust of this chicken pot pie.